Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives, 1885-2017 and undated RL.00963
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- REGULATION SERIES, 1909-1981 (bulk 1956-1973)
  - General Regulatory Materials (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
    - Industry Proposals
      - Model Ordinance: Uniform Regulation for Electrical Advertising Outdoor Advertising, 1931 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
      - Model State Law 112532, ca. 1932 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
      - Model 3-Proposed State Act by W.E. Beehan, undated (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
      - Model 6-Regulation of Commercial State Enterprises, undated (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
    - Tentative Plan Project
      - Advertisers' Reactions, 1932-1935 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
        [File of J.B. Stewart, Legal and Legislative Div.; Highway survey; Coca-Cola space; confidential letter; Mrs. Elizabeth B. Lawton; License and Permit Bill approved by OAAA at French Lick, Indiana (Annotated); Analysis of items suggested for inclusion in Rural Outdoor Advertising Legislation, with summary of police power]
      - American Federation of Arts, 1920-1932 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
        [Contact Reports Concerning Educational Platform 1932; Poor Richard's Almanac 1920; article reprints- Ad Man Resents Slur on Craft, Outdoor Displays as Art Galleries 1920; Bulletin of the Municipal Art Society 1926; American Magazine of Art 1920 and 1926; journal articles 1920-1928; report- Pennell (mayor of New York) Calls Billboard Ads Crime Against Art 1920]
      - City Club, 1932 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
      - National Grange, 1931-1933 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
        [Correspondence; new clippings; Pennsylvania Grange News; contact report]
      - National Parks Service, 1932-1941 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
        [Article from Saturday Evening Post-The National Domain and the New Deal, 1933; Natural Scenic Beauties; contact reports]
      - State Federation of Women's Clubs, 1932-1933 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
        [Correspondence; report and suggestions for remedial legislation; confidential letter to Wisconsin FWC; photos of group, mostly women; report on Inspection of Outdoor Advertising on Tennessee Highways; Wyoming legislation]
      - State Garden Clubs, 1931-1942 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
        [Program for Roadside Beauty Forum; general handwritten notes; correspondence; Bulletin of National Council of State Garden Clubs, Inc. 1938 and 1942; legislative report on National Council of State Garden Clubs; flyer-Billboards Destroy Motoring Joy; NCSGC By-laws and procedure for the Organization of State Garden Club Federation 1929; NBOL (Natural Beauties of Landscape)]
  - Interest Groups
    - American Automobile Association, 1925 and undated (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
    - American Automobile Association-Club Posters, 1937-1940 ( Fisk's File) (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
    - American Nature Association, 1930-1938 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
      [Booklet- American Nature Association Quarterly Bulletin; article reprint; copies of article; correspondence; Tentative Plan for the Preservation of the Natural Scenic Beauties; Lawton surveys made by Mr. and Mrs. W.L. Lawton]
    - American Road Builders Association, 1923-1949 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
      [Modesty on billboards; wartime manpower; The Road Ahead, 1945; news-letter; legislative bulletin; national highway users; conference-Roadside Advertising Abuse 1925, 1945; Sixth International Road Congress, Washington, D.C., 1930; What about Country Highways, dated 1921; excerpts from Magic Motorways, 1949]
    - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1932-1945 (Box RG36 -Legal Size)
      [File of Judge E. Allen Frost; Contact reports concerning Education Platform; Washington Conference; Quebec Bill No. 54-An act respecting signboard and posters; suggestions for Amenities Bill; report-Proposed Public Relation Platform and Legislative Policy of OAAA; glossary of terms; report on preparation of Educational Platform; steps for development of Public Relations Platform and Legislative Program; Federal Reporter-City of Cincinnati vs. Vester, Richards et al, Reakirt-condemnation of property; A Bill for an Act to Create a State-wide Scenic Highway System for the Protection of the Natural Beauties of Landscape]
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs (GFWC) Outdoor Advertising correspondence, 1920-1938 (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
      [National Council for Protection of Roadside Beauty; contact reports; news clippings; Wood Poster Advertising Company; Booklets- Modern Outdoor Advertising-Its Policies and Practice, If Standardized Outdoor Advertising Did Not Exist; reference to GFWC booklet- Save the Beauty of America-The Landscape is No Place for Advertising-Are you Interested in Banishing Offensive Billboards from the American Landscape?; article- How to Sell Automobiles in Chicago; General Federation News; Mrs. Max Lane]
      [See also Box RG3]
    - General Opposition to Outdoor Advertising -Clippings, 1928-1937 (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - National Highway Users Conference, 1945-1958 (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - Roadside Business Association, 1936-1953 (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
      [Congressman Jennings Randolph (W.Va.), Randolph Amendment to the Interregional Highway Bill, War Production Board, Highway Bill S. 21d05, small signs manufacturers; meetings]
    - Roadside Business Groups, 1947-1952, 2 folders (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
      [Roadside Business Association; legislative efforts, state legislation, by-laws, meetings]
    - Standard Oil Company of California, 1928 (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
  - Legislation - Federal (Chronological Subseries)
    [See also Boxes RG4-RG18]
    - 1917, H.R. 4280 -War Revenue Bill (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - 1917-1918, S. 2985 -War Revenue Bill (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - 1920-1922, H.R. 12976 -Tax on Advertising (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - 1921-1930, Taxes on Advertising-Miscellaneous (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - 1933-1934, H.R. 7835 -Coconut Oil Tax (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - 1933-1934, S.R. 1944 -Federal Food and Drugs Act (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - 1940, H.R. 10720 -Defense Funding Bill (Outdoor Advertising Tax) (Box RG37 -Legal Size)
    - 1941, H.R. 5417 -Revenue Act, 2 folders (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
    - 1941, H.R. 5417, 77th Congress, 1st Session: Revenue Act of 1941-Tax on Outdoor Advertising (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
      [Extract from hearing; Finance Committee of U.S. Senate; H.R. 10720; news clippings; report on newspaper clippings; Special Bulletin re: Revenue Bill]
    - 1942, H.R. 5990 -Emergency Price Control Act (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
    - 1943-1947, Federal Highway Act -Senate S. 2105, H.R. 4915 (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
      [U.S. Conf. and Referendum #180, etc.]
    - 1944-1952, Federal Highway Act of 1944: Prints, Amendments to 1952 (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
    - 1944, United States Federal Highway Act of 1944, S. 2105 (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
    - 1944, H.R. 4915 Amendment to Highway Act of 1944 (Papers) (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
    - 1944, Confidential Bulletin on H.R. 5040 (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
    - 1979, FHWA Hearings-Correspondence (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
    - 1979, FHWA Hearings-News Articles (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
    - [1979], Hearings, Folders 1-2 of 4 (Box RG38 -Legal Size)
      [U.S. Department of Transportation; hearing docket; lists]
    - [1979], Hearings, Folders 3-4 of 4 (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
  - Legislation - State
    [See also Boxes RG19-RG21]
    - California, 1945-1952 (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
    - Poster Panel Comparison, 1976-1982, 2 folders (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
      [Cost schedules; panel compensation]
  - Litigation - Federal Judiciary
    [See also Box RG21]
    - U.S. vs. OAAA Anti-Trust Case, 1950. (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
      [Brochure- Outdoor Advertising Simplified1929?; Civil Action no. 50 C 935-(Sherman Act); U.S. vs. Outdoor Advertising... 1950; pamphlet-economic fact...in Iowa 1931; Report of the Committee on Reorganization Plans 1946; recommendations for 1932 program-director's meeting 1931; Public Policy brochure 1933; Rain-Lap Posters brochure 1941; Sales Prospectus: Building Supply Trade 1928]
  - Litigation - State Judiciary
    [See also Boxes RG21-RG23]
    - Ghaster Properties/ Ghaster Outdoor vs. Highways of State of Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
    - Litigation on Outdoor Advertising, 1893-1975, 3 folders (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
      [Law Generally (correspondence; news clipping copy; study of cases made by Ruth Johnson; list of decisions pertaining to outdoor advertising); Alabama to Vermont]
    - Proceedings- Shulman vs. People, 1960 (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
      [Persons owning land in view of state highway vs. state of New York]
  - Media Clippings
    [See also Boxes RG23-RG24]
    - Inez Robb, 1963 ( Chicago Daily News columnist) (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
      [Fan letter; news clippings and copies; letter to editor against Inez Robb; possible libel action against Inez Robb]
  - Regulatory Administration
    - Bureau of Public Roads
      [See also Box RG28]
      - Papers, 1929-1939 (Box RG39 -Legal Size)
      - Papers, 1940-1953 (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
    - Commission on Americans Outdoors, 1985-1987 (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
      [National Recreation Study; News reprints; booklet-Americans and the Outdoors by the President's commission on American Outdoors; White House announcement; proposed report outline and recommendations; issue of National Inhalers Association; draft of meeting agenda; staff report; proposed public hearings]
    - Department of Commerce, 1928-1945 (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
      [ Alabama State-Local Businessmen's Organization; booklet-Markets after the War; Census of Business, Wholesale Trade; War-time advertising exhibits; photo; Bureau of Foreign and Domestic Commerce; Trade Association survey; confidential government report-census of manufacturers, 1935]
    - Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1976-1987 (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
      [Guidelines for commercial vitalization area of Birmingham; boulevard development area plans-preliminary layout plans; conspiracy between HUD and city planners]
  - Research
    [See also Box RG30]
    - Highway Research Board, undated (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
      [Reports by states of railroad, highway, industry, farming, mining, resorts, if contained in that state]
  - Topics and Controversies
    - Billboard Controversy
      [See also Box RG33]
      - Papers, 1916-1939, 1950s, 2 folders (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
    - Billboards -State Regulation
      [See also Box RG34]
      - New York -Tallamy Thruway Contract, 1961 (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
      - North Carolina, 1964 (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
    - Land Use
      - National Land Use Policy, 1970-1974, 3 folders (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
        [ Land Use and Planning Assistance Act: Report of the Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs: United States Senate; Congressional Record; Special Report-Land Use Legislation]
        [1974 book- Land Use Planning Act of 1974; congressional record; news reprint; position paper of OAAA with regard to HR 10294-Land Use Planning Act of 1974; Union Catalog books-HR 10295 and HR13790-Land Use Planning Assistance Act; correspondence; The Congressional Monitor; HR 16028-To Establish Land Use Policy; booklet- Proposed Municipals Land Use Law
        [folder-1970-1972 article reprints; Statement of Chairman Train (Council on Environmental Quality) before Senate Interior Committee on S. 3354-National Land Use Policy Act of 1970; HR 7211-Public Land Policy Act of 1971; statement of National Association of Manufacturers on S. 632 and S. 992 before committee on Interior and Insular Affairs of Senate; Coastal Zone Management statement of position; news clippings-Senator Edmund S. Muskie and Senator Henry Jackson; booklet-Land Use and Planning Assistance Act of 1972]
    - Licensing
      - License and Permit Act, [ 1932] (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
      - OAAA Licensing and Permit Bill Approved Friday 1932 Oct. 28 ( E. Allen Frost) (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
        [Bill of OAAA adopted at French Lick convention; analysis of items suggested by National Council for Protection of Roadside Beauty accompanied by Summary of Police Power and its Limitation]
    - Tobacco Advertising
      [See also Box RG35]
      - Detailed Comparison of HR 1824 and S. 772, undated (Box RG40 -Legal Size)
- RESEARCH SERIES, 1924-1980 (bulk 1950-1970)
  The series collects reports on research relating to nearly every aspect of outdoor advertising, including attitudes toward billboards, campaign coverage, legibility studies, market surveys, and public opinion polls. There are also reports on market research methodologies, and data analysis. Many prominent research firms are represented here, including Axiom, Barney Link, Bruskin Associates, Daniel Starch, A.C. Nielsen, Simmons Market Research Bureau, and Wilbur Smith.
  - Advertising Research Foundation (ARF) (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
    - National Window Display Research, 1937 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
  - Arthur D. Little
    - Study- A Study of Human Response to Visual Environments in Urban Areas, 1966-1967 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
  - Association of National Advertisers (ANA)
    - Advertising Agency Compensation, 1934 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
    - Color in Magazine Advertising, 1931 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
  - Associations
    - Highway Research Board, 1947-1952 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
    - Traffic Institute of Northwestern University, Northwestern University, 1952-1959 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
  - Axiom Market Research Bureau, Inc./ Audiences Market by Market for Outdoor (AMRB-AMMO)
    - Markets, 1976-1979 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
    - Target Group Index (TGI), 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
    - TGI Outdoor in a Nutshell, [1979] (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
    - TGI Plan, 1978 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
  - Barney Link Fellowship
    - Fellowship Meeting, 1927 (Box RS1 -Letter Size)
    - Fellowship Studies, 1924-1930 (Box RS2 -Letter Size)
  - Beetle Boards
    - Summary of Research, 1977 (Box RS2 -Letter Size)
  - Brandt/ Faison
    - Poster Copy Isolation Study, 1955 and undated (Box RS2 -Letter Size)
  - Brennan, John
    - What Some Key Advertising Agency Executives Think of Various Advertising Media, 1946 (Box RS2 -Letter Size)
  - Bruskin Associates
    - Boston Transit Study
      - Awareness of Exterior Bus-Trolley, Interior Bus-Trolley-Subway and Trolley-Subway Station Poster Advertising, 1968 Mar. (Box RS2 -Letter Size)
      - 14-Day Reach and Frequency Exterior and Interior Advertising, 1967 Nov.-Dec. (Box RS2 -Letter Size)
    - Detroit Transit Study
      - 14-Day Reach and Frequency Exterior and Interior Advertising, April-May 1968 (Box RS2 -Letter Size)
    - New York Transit Study (Box RS3 -Letter Size)
      - Awareness of Exterior Bus, Bus-O-Rama, and Interior Bus Advertising, 1968 May (Box RS3 -Letter Size)
    - Philadelphia Transit Survey
      - Awareness of Exterior Bus-Trolley, Interior Bus-Trolley-Subway and Trolley-Subway Station Poster Advertising, 1968 Mar. (Box RS3 -Letter Size)
  - Bureau of Public Roads
    - Peripheral Land Study, 1966 (Box RS3 -Letter Size)
  - Coverage
    [See also Box RS12]
    - Billboard Placement, 1955 (Box RS3 -Letter Size)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box RS3 -Letter Size)
      [ Lawrence O. Holmes (plan of action to improve the outdoor industry image)]
    - Determining Adequate Coverage, 1930 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
      [ John Paver- resolutions providing for proper method of determining adequate coverage of city or town...; suggested information pamphlet; progress report, etc.]
    - Equalized Showings- Lexington, Kentucky, 1938 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
      [Exhibits: Lexington, Kentucky; analysis of Poster Plant Member's Statement]
    - Equalized Showings- Terre Haute, Indiana, 1938 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
    - Markets- Small Town, 1932-1960 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
    - Markets- Winter Advertising, 1940 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
    - Media, 1925-1975 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence, poster remembrance and identification norms by sex and product classification, Highway Beautification Act of 1965]
    - Media- Spectacolor, undated (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
    - Mobile Media, 1980-1983 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
    - Percentage Showing Plan, 1940 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence with National Directors and State Secretaries (concerning Reasons Why brief)]
    - Recapitulation of 100 coverage by States, 1936-1947 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
    - Reports- Manual of Poster Advertising Coverage, 1952, 1955, 4 folders (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
    - Resolutions, Formulae, Coverage, etc., 1930 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
    - Showing Allotments, 1918-1949 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
      [Booklets- The Policy Method and Procedure for the Determination of Poster Advertising Coverage Allotments, Suggestions as to How to Check a Poster Showing plant, dated 1921]
    - Showings, 1938-1940 (Box RS4 -Letter Size)
      [Equalization Procedure (memorandum for discussion, correspondence, graphs, charts)]
  - Sign Legibility, 1941-1980, 2 folders (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
    [A means to establish index of visibility, visual communication research-slide of legibility: Midnight Cowboy, copies of J.H. Prince articles, state of the art on legibility and target value of signs; signs, color and legibility; reports, booklet-Highway Research Record, 1973]
  - Crossley
    - Calibration Studies, 1982 (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
  - Daniel Starch
    - Circulation Households-Men and Women Readers, 1971 (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
      [Copy of a 1970 supplement to ANA's publication Magazine Circulation and Rate Trends]
    - Goods/Services Activities, 1969, 2 folders (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
    - Poster Audiences, 1956-1958 (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
    - Poster Remembrance, 1962 (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
    - Products Report-Circulation Households, 1972 (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
    - Products Report-Males and Females-Primary and Total Audiences, 1972, 2 folders (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
    - Readership-City vs. Suburb, 1961-1967 (Box RS5 -Letter Size)
    - Young People Report, ( Youth Market) 1972 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
    - Starch / Hooperating Media Report: 1971 [Study of Eighty Magazines--Primary and Total Audiences] (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
  - Financial Advertisers Association
    - Research Report on Outdoor Advertising, 1926 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
  - Foster & Kleiser
    - Poster Design Analysis, 1968-1981 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
  - General Outdoor
    - Psychological Impact Study, 1949 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
  - Harris Donovan
    - Outdoor planning, 1987-1988 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
  - Haug/ T. Scope
    - Methodology, 1970-1975 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
      [Report on Outdoor Design KIIS: Presented to Wilton, Coombs and Colnett; 1970 Nov. 11: Los Angeles by Haug Associates]
  - Institute of Outdoor Advertising (IOA)
    - Calibration Research Bids, 1981 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
  - Market Math
    - Calibration Study, 1975 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
  - Markets
    - Analysis of Poster Markets Served by More than One Plant Owner, 1958 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
    - Lawton Surveys, undated (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959-1963 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
    - Publications- Metropolitan Markets, 1932 (Box RS6 -Letter Size)
    - Publications- Metropolitan Markets, 1934 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
    - Reports- Outdoor Advertising Circulation and Rate Relationships, 1960 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
    - Study-Media to Markets Pilot, 1962 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
      [Media to Market for the State of Indiana: Confidential-Not for Publication]
    - Surveys- A Survey of the Market of the Outdoor Advertising Industry, ca. 1928 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
  - Media
    - A Test of the Relative Effectiveness of Outdoor Billboards vs. Radio, 1963 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, 1953-1963 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
  - Nielsen
    - Nielsen Researcher, 1964-1965 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
  - Norms
    - Readership Norms, 1954-1959 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
      [(Handwritten on inside cover -Cal State Survey--Bran Standings: Real Estate--Options: Turkey Export: Pre-testing--Field: -J&B; Analysis--LEC FTC: OAI: Magazine Readership L.A. -) (readership and correct identification; folders--Product Group Averages, Painted Display Norms, Product Group Averages)]
  - Novelties
    - Cards and Inserts, 1953-1965 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
      [ Koppel Post Cards (handwritten on folder--Castonian: Al Koppel Print: 5-4270; Hawthorne: 7-3151; Mr. Missan--Mr. Wolt) advertisement for novelty products--match books, figurines, post card, calendars, 1956; advertising postcards; prices list, correspondence]
  - OAAA -Outdoor Advertising Association of America
    - Memory Span for Posters, 1930 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
    - Product Classification Plan, 1961 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
    - Publication- The Happy Medium: A Case Study on How to Select Media to Increase Sales, 1960 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
    - Report-Outdoor Poster Panel and Bulletin Advertising, 1957 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
    - Target Research- Texaco, Maxwell House, R.T. French, 1963 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
  - OAI -Outdoor Advertising Inc.
    - A Profile of Outdoor Advertising Readers, 1963 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
    - Market Penetration: A Study of Comparative Circulation Values, 1931 (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
  - Ohio State University
    - Legibility Study, 1958-1963, 3 folders (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
  - Oxtoby-Smith
    - Proposal-Confidential Prospectus for IOA, undated (Box RS7 -Letter Size)
  - John Paver (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - How to Select Retail Store Locations, 1936? (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
  - Plan One
    - Normative Data Outcome, 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
  - Popai/ Dupont
    - Consumer Buying Habits, 1977-1978 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
  - Population
    - Average Cost per Thousand N.A.C. per Representative Display by Population Groups, 1935 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Birkholz Report- Some Statistical and Mathematical Notes on Poster Advertising Allotments and Populations, undated (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Census, 1950-1955 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
      [Census of industrial trade and transportation]
    - Correspondence, 1932-1962 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1951-1980 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Paint Town, 1954 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Policy, 1936-1949 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Sales Management Population Estimates (Census), 1949-1956 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
  - Poster Appraisal Service
    - Bakery Scores, 1963 and undated (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Copy Survey Methods, 1949-1950 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
      [ University of California; news clipping]
    - General Information, 1960 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Poster Scores-#50 and #100 Showings, 1955 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Procedures, 1950-1964 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Readership Norms, 1963-1964 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - Survey Objectives and Instructions, 1961-1965 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
  - PRS
    - Audience, 1983-1985 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
  - Public Opinion Surveys
    - Arthur D. Little Study, 1965-1969 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - California- Fieldscope, 1971 (Box RS8 -Letter Size)
    - California- Information Centers, 1973-1979, 3 folders (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Caravan Studies, 1972 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Columbus, Ohio, 1982 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Dallas, Texas, 1978 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Florida by Linda Ann Watson, 1976 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - General, 1937-1952 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Greenville, South Carolina, undated (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Harris Environment Survey, 1979 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Houston Chronicle Poll, 1991 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Kiosks/ InfoSites, 1968-1975 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1979 (Box RS9 -Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1980, 2 folders (Box RS9 -Letter Size)